Family Planning Advocates of New York State; Records apap044
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications and Reports, Undated; 5; 0.5 cubic ft.
  - When the Conventional Wisdom is Wrong: A Reexamination of the Role of Abortion As an Issue in Federal Elections, 1974-86, 1988 (Box 3 (5-Publications and Reports), Folder 21)
  - New York's Children in 1989: Society at Risk, A Report of New York State Project 2000 (Box 3 (5-Publications and Reports), Folder 22)
  - Reproductive Health Initiative for FY 1990-91: A Proposal to Promote Early Intervention for Adolescents and Low Income Women, 1989 (Box 3 (5-Publications and Reports), Folder 23)
  - Teenage Pregnancy and Too-Early Childbearing: Public Costs, Personal Consequences, 1990 (Box 3 (5-Publications and Reports), Folder 24)
  - The Facts Speak Louder: Planned Parenthood's Critique of 'The Silent Scream', Undated (Box 3 (5-Publications and Reports), Folder 25)
  - Fact Sheets, ca. 1995-2000 (Box 12 (5-Publications and Reports), Folder 1)
  - Reproductive Health Laws and Regulations, 2000 (Box 12 (5-Publications and Reports), Folder 2)